ZOHAIB

AFRIDI

(540) 214 9820 ****zohaib0126@gmail.com **≥**/in/zohaib-a/ **in**



INTRODUCTION

Junior at James Madison University seeking an internship or entry-level position in software or web development. Experience with multiple programming languages and art with 1-year worth of professional experience. Advocate for functionality in user interface and experience.



CERTIFICATES

HTML5 & CSS3 Certificate | Udemy 05/2018



PROJECTS

HTML5 & CSS3 Final Project | Udemy

https://zoheezus.github.io/Omnifood/



SKILLS

JAVA NODE.JS
HTML5 & CSS3 MICROSOFT OFF.
PYTHON PHOTOSHOP
JAVASCRIPT MANAGEMENT



INTERESTS

For years, I have had an interest in technology, programming languages, computer science, computer builds, videogames, and the arts. I am always looking for ways to combine science, art, and reasoning and how they can influence each other.



EDUCATION

Integrated Science & Technology
| James Madison University
2016 - PRESENT
| Minor in Art
| James Madison University
2016 - PRESENT



EXPERIENCE

Web Developer | Rocktown Motors 02/2016 – PRESENT

Designed and developed website for local car dealership. Managing social media ads. Transferring content to new site.

Dispatcher | Royal Cab

2014 - PRESENT

Managing and directing taxi drivers to the locations of customers. Coordinating w/medical transportation companies and finding suitable transportation for patients.

Teacher Assistant | Eastern Mennonite University

05/2017 - 08/2017

Planning committee to develop curriculum for a 1-week long camp for EMU's Interfaith Peace Camp. Member of Faculty & Staff